本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作，仅供学习，禁止用于任何商业盈利行为。若因私自散布传播造成法律问题，本字幕组概不负责。更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组。
云九商店的顾客请注意
Attention, Cloud 9 shoppers,
商店将会在20分钟后关门
the store has been closed for 20 minutes.
届时商店员工都会下班
Many of us would like to leave.
如果此时您还在购物
So, if you're still in the store,
EVERYONE
您就是个混蛋
you're being a dick.
关注新浪微博
@大家字幕组
别那么讨嫌
Don't be a dick.
扫扫加微信
太难了 我得和这个垃圾桶朝夕相处
It's tough, because I have to live
大家字幕组
你懂吧?
with this trash can, you know?
微 信 关 注
dajiazimuzu
没错 我理解
Right. No, I get it.
dajiazimuzu
这是一个非常重要的决定
It's a very big decision.
你可以今晚回家 好好睡一觉
So, you know, maybe you could go home tonight, sleep on it,
扫扫加微信
明天再来选?
and decide tomorrow?
dajiazimuzu
扫扫加微信
大家字幕组
不行 我昨天就说"明天再选"
No, "Decide tomorrow" is what I said yesterday.
如果我不回家为期中考试做准备
If I don't get home and study for my midterm,
我就死定了
I'm totally screwed.
嘿 你看起来好美
Oh, hey, you look so cute.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚有我的高年级舞蹈演出
It's my senior dance recital tonight.
不会吧? 为什么不和我们说?
What? Why didn't you tell us?
是啊 我不能上台 因为这个
Well, I can't perform because of, you know, this.
不过我要去给其他姑娘们加油
But I'm gonna go and cheer on the other girls.
那也得等这大哥离开商店
Yeah, if this bozo ever leaves the store.
嘿 默特尔 快讲讲你切除子宫的故事
Hey, Myrtle, go bust out your hysterectomy story.
没事 交给我吧
It's all right. I got it.
那是1953年
It was 1953,
医学科学风靡一时
and medical science was all the rage.
翻译  糖糖 累
我们刚收到了你们寄来的标志牌
The thing is, you just sent us the shipment of signs now,
我很讨厌星期五晚上
and I'd hate to keep people late
让大家加班
on a Friday evening to hang them all up.
校对  累
如果有人听到了我的信息 请马上打给我好吗?
So, if anyone gets this message, could you call me back, please?
我是格林
It's Glenn.
时间轴  马路边
- 先生 － 不好意思
- Sir. - Oh, sorry.
不好意思 先生
Oh, oh, so sorry, sir.
- 先生 我实在是... - 是我挡路了
- Sir, I can't quite... - Oh, I am in the way.
- 是的 - 工作需要
- Yeah. - Duty calls.
不好意思 我好像不能...
Sorry. I can't seem to...
压制  宋胖子
那边有块污渍
There's a spot right over there.
- 是的 - 好吧
- Yeah. - Okay.
这是《虎胆龙威2》吗?
Hey, is that "Die Hard 2"?
这是《虎胆龙威》系列最棒的一部
That is the best "Die Hard."
祝您有个美好的夜晚
Have a heavenly night.
好吧
Okay.
马特奥 干得漂亮
Oh, great job, Mateo. Great job.
我们得留下来加班了
Hey, we're all staying late to do more work.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我也是刚发现
I just found out about it.
真的很抱歉
I feel terrible about this.
超级商店
第一季 第八集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品
我还得加1到2个小时的班 帮我留着座位
I'm stuck at work for an hour or two, but save my seat.
我一定会尽快过去的
I'll be there as soon as I can.
你必须要来啊 婊贝
You have to get here, bitch.
我知道 婊贝
I know, bitch.
鸟宝宝们 我是妈咪 听着
Birds, it's Mommy. Listen up.
侦察兵 太妃糖 罗斯福 皮卡丘 你们要照顾好大家
Scout, Taffy, FDR, Pikachu, you guys are in charge,
像个头儿一样 我知道你们能行
so act like the leaders I know that you are.
鹦鹉宝宝们 我想你们可能听不到我的话
Now, cockatoos, I assume you can't hear me right now
你们应该已经睡着了
since you should all be asleep already.
宝宝们 听好了
Okay, heads down.
公司弄错了吧
Ooh, corporate messed up.
这些跟我们刚取下来的一毛一样
Those are the same signs we just took down.
不是吧
I don't think so.
不对 他们说旧的标志牌是
Nope, they say the old signs
暗淡的 过时的"海豚色"
were this pale, outdated color called "Glossy dolphin."
新的标志牌是醒目的 振奋人心的
The new ones are a bold, exciting color
"海豚色B版"
called "Glossy dolphin B."
挺有意思的 对吧?
This is kind of fun, right?
站这么高
Being up high like this?
让我想起了玩室内攀岩的日子
Reminds me of my indoor rock-climbing days.
我只想赶快回家复习期中考试
I just need to get home to study for my midterm.
期中考试
Midterm.
让我想到过去
That takes me back.
临时抱佛脚... 或者说是试图
Cramming for tests... or trying to.
半数时间 我最后会
Half the time, I'd just end up getting drunk
别人的房间醉的一塌糊涂
in someone's dorm room
整晚都在"深交"
and spend the whole night having "Deep conversations."
真好玩
That's so fun.
我跟你讲过我那时
Did I ever tell you the story about that one time
成年后上大学
when I went to college as a grown-up
半工半读还得承担所有责任?
and I had to go work and I had all these responsibilities?
真是笑尿了
It's a laugh riot.
你不需要抓着梯子的
You don't have to hold the ladder, you know.
我不会让你掉下来的...
I'm not gonna let you fall...
不会在我的眼皮底下
not on my watch.
嘿 看看呐
Oh, hey, look at that.
太酷了 牛仔
Ooh, cool move, cowboy.
你说这个?
What, this?
我生来就是用电钻的料
I was born with a drill in my hand.
我家以前有个五金店...
My family used to own a hardware store...
"斯特吉斯父子"?
Sturgis and Sons?
没错 过去59年里
Yeah, for 59 years,
"斯特吉斯"就是工具的代名词
the name "Sturgis" Was synonymous with tools...
直到这条街上开了云九商店
well, until Cloud 9 moved in up the street,
一个月后 我们就关门了
and then a month later, we lost everything.
嘿 有人见过激光水准仪吗?
Hey, has anyone seen the laser level?
给他们打工不会让你觉得有点不爽吗?
Doesn't it make you a little angry to be working for them?
我不会浪费时间与愤怒为伍
Oh, I don't waste my time with anger.
看看啊 我砸到指头了
Look at that. I hit my finger.
看起来很严重
That looked pretty serious.
所有灯都灭了吗?
Did the lights go out?
拜托
Oh, come on.
格林 灯怎么灭了?
Glenn, what's up with the lights?
我有点赶
I'm kind of in a rush.
所有的灯由总公司控制
Actually, the lights are controlled by corporate.
什么鬼?
What?
每晚固定时间
Every night at a certain time,
会自动关灯锁门
the lights dim, and the doors automatically lock.
所有门都锁了?
All the doors lock?
是的
Yep.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
拜托 拜托 拜托
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
不是吧 开什么玩笑?
Oh, no, no, no, no. Are you kidding me?
不要啊!
No!
好吧 坏消息是我们被锁在这里了
Okay, the bad news is we're locked in.
迪娜和我去办公室
Dina and I will go to my office
找找开锁密码
and look for the lock override code.
这段时间你们继续挂标志牌
In the meantime, you guys keep putting up signs.
你们可以从中找点乐子
You can make a game out of it.
你们可以叫这个游戏"标志牌狂欢"
You can call the game "Signage Fever."
我才不要玩那个游戏
I am not playing that game.
- 大伙... - 不要
- Guys... - No.
你都不知道我要说什么
You don't even know what I was gonna say.
我知道每次你一说"大伙"
I know that every time you start a sentence
就一定会说
with, "Guys," You end it with,
"让我们拼尽全力"或者"让我们找点乐子"
"Let's make the best of this," Or, "Let's have fun."
你绝对不会说"大伙 这简直糟透了"
You never say, "Guys, this really sucks."
大伙 现在整个商店尽在我们手中
Guys, we have the entire store to ourselves.
我们可以为所欲为
We could do whatever we want.
如果我们想要找乐子
If we decide that this is gonna be fun,
就能找到
then this is gonna be fun.
如果你们想跟我一起 我在
So, if you're with me, I will see all of you
娱乐区等着你们
in the fun zone.
"娱乐区"?
"Fun zone"?
有时我真想扇他
Sometimes I just really want to slap him.
我想就在公司给我的备忘录当中
I think it was on one of these memos from corporate.
给你
Here.
- "帮派流行语" - "如何发现帮派"
- "Union buzzwords." - "How to spot a union."
"反帮派措施"
"Anti-union activity."
"如果听到'帮派'该怎么做"
"What to do if you hear the word 'union.'"
"报告帮派行为"
"Reporting union activity."
"有毒食品召回名单"?
"List of toxic food recalls"?
我不记得召回过什么食品
I don't remember doing any food recalls.
怎么了?
What?
"员工手册政策调整附录..."
"Addendum of policy changes to employee handbook..."
"取消禁止上下级恋爱
"Relationships between supervisors and subordinates
改为不鼓励"
no longer forbidden, now just strongly discouraged."
文字游戏而已 噢 在这里
Yeah, words. Oh, here it is.
"请取下附带的卡片
"Please detach the accompanying card
并放置在安全的地方"
and keep in a safe place."
看 我写着"比如车里"
And, look, I wrote, "Like in your car,"
我在"车"加了下划线
and then I underlined "Car."
就是说卡就在外面
Oh, that means it's just outside.
好吧 坏消息是
Okay, the bad news
我把密码卡放在车上的小柜里了
is I left the card with the code in my glove compartment.
我让我太太来取卡片
So I called my wife to come get it,
但我们只有一辆车
but we only have one car,
所以她得等她妹妹送她过来
so she has to wait for her sister to come get her.
大伙儿 外面有个人
You guys, there's someone out there.
嘿!嘿!
Oh, my God. Hey! Hey!
你能帮我从车里取个东西吗?
Can you get something from my car?
我们要啵 啵 啵 啵
We need a boop-boop-boop-boop.
你们要错过了哦
You guys are missing out.
呵呵哒 多特别的经历哟
What a unique experience it must be,
骑着有轮子的车满商店逛
moving around a store on wheels.
钥匙在轮胎上
The key's above the tire.
卡片在仪表盘的小柜里
Get card from glove compartment.
把卡拿过来
Bring card here.
我们要出去了!
Whoo! We're gonna get out of here!
- 是那吗? 是那吗? - 等等... 哦 棒呆
- Is it there? Is it there? - Wait, wait... oh, good.
看 他拿到钥匙了
Look, he's got the key.
为什么他要上了驾驶员的位置?
Why is he getting in the driver's seat?
不 你不需要发动汽车
No, you don't need to start the engine
开柜子就行
to open the glove compartment.
不 你不需要开车
No, you don't need to move the car.
等等 你要去哪?
Wait. Where are you going?
他要去哪?
Where's he going?
什么 哪里...
What the-where is the...
在娱乐区穿梭...
Cruising through the fun zone...
嘿 你能...
Hey, can you maybe...
好吧
Okay.
我有一点庆幸错过了演出
Part of me's glad I missed the recital.
我从六年级开始
I've been looking forward to my senior dance
就一直很期待高年级舞蹈演出
since sixth grade,
如果只能坐在那里看着真是逊爆了
and it would've sucked to just sit there and watch.
我不是说后悔有了这个宝宝
I'm not saying that I regret this baby.
我只是觉得如果能晚点...
I just wish that I'd had it later...
或者早点 像我很多朋友那样
or sooner, like a lot of my friends.
你们知道我的意思吧?
You know what I mean?
我知道 是的
Uh, I do, yes,
我想我们每个人都有后悔的事情
and I think each and every one of us has regrets.
我接着说
I'll go next.
我后悔去海上学府
I regret doing Semester at Sea
而不是选一个国家
instead of just picking one country
去吸收它的文化
and really absorbing the culture.
还有谁?
Who else?
我唯一后悔总是想太多
Well, my only regrets are the times I overthought things
不随性而为
and didn't go for what I wanted.
- 就是 - 为什么要抑制本性呢?
- There you go. - I mean, why fight nature?
人之初 性本兽 对吧?
We're all just animals, right?
我真后悔没有从海浪中救出我的双胞胎弟弟
I regret not rescuing my twin brother from that wave.
就是这样 大伙儿
So there you have it, guys.
我们现在更加了解彼此了
We are learning lots about each other.
你呢 小艾?
What about you, Ame?
你最大的遗憾是什么?
What are you... What's your biggest regret?
我想是我年轻的时候没有上大学
I guess I regret not going to college
不然我就有很多故事
when I was younger so that I could have lots of stories
烦我的同事了
to annoy my coworkers with.
起码现在很安静
Hey, well, at least it's quiet.
不用听他们让我们放的蠢爆了的背景音乐了
We don't have to listen to that stupid Muzak they make us play.
我其实有点喜欢那音乐
I actually kind of like the music.
让我感觉整天都在等电话
It makes me feel like I'm on hold all day.
格林 这里的一切你都喜欢
Glenn, you like everything about this store.
真是个怪人
That's weird, man.
我也不是什么都喜欢的
I don't like everything about this store.
讲真 雇员洗手间的后防溅板
Truth be told, the backsplash in the employee's bathroom--
最多是个B-
it's, like, B-minus, at best.
这就是公司让你唯一不爽的地方?
That's the only thing that bugs you about this company?
过道间隔也有点太近了...
Well, I guess the aisles are a bit too close together...
有时负责人
and sometimes the folks in charge
不把我当人看
don't treat me like I'm a human being with feelings.
是啊 确实挺烦
Yeah, that's a bummer.
"斯特吉斯父子"就像个大家庭一样
Sturgis and Sons was a community.
顾客们总会说"嗨 格林
Customers would be like, "Hi, Glenn.
你有这么大的螺丝吗?"
Do you have a screw in such-and-such a size?"
我会说"可能有吧
And I'd say, "I think so.
问问我爸爸"
Maybe ask my dad."
那时就像天堂一样
It was paradise.
你们知道我还后悔什么吗? 那次...
You know what else I regret? That time...
之后就有了这家连锁商店
And then this chain moves in.
这破玩意从哪来的? 让我们深夜加班...
I mean, where do they get off? Keep us late in...
锁在黑黑的商店里
locked in the dark, you know,
无一不触碰我们的底线
all in service of the bottom line.
继续
Yeah. Go.
我恨这领带
I hate this tie.
我恨这衬衣!
I hate this shirt!
- 好吧 - 那不是他的衬衣吗?
- Okay. - Isn't that his shirt?
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
噢 你有点过了
Oh, you're going a little too far now.
大家字幕组
我也恨区域经理迪克·拉森
And I hate Regional Manager Dicky Larson,
可你们知道我最恨什么吗?
but you know what I hate most of all?
大家字幕组
我恨云九
I hate Cloud 9.
刚才怎么了?
What just happened?
我想我们把格林玩坏了
I think we broke Glenn.
噢 这些都坏了
Oh, no, this is damaged.
我们不能出售了 没错
Guess we can't sell these. Right.
开始趴体 小婊砸们
It's a party, mother-fathers,
"斯特吉斯父子"赞助
sponsored by Sturgis and Sons.
- 你 你 你 到你了... - 刚才那个不错
- You, you, you, you, you, you... - That was good.
好
Okay.
我从来没有...
Never have I ever...
上架过冰淇淋
Stocked ice cream.
好的 但... 和那差不多
Okay, but... You know, like that,
但更极端一点的
but, like, a little more edgy.
比如说
You know, like, not this, but,
"我从来没吃过人肉"
"Never have I ever eaten human flesh."
别 别 别
Oh, no, no, no.
喝了就说明你干过这事
You drink if you have done it.
宝宝明白
Mm-hmm. I understand.
我又有一个
I have another one.
我从来没在店里打过炮
Never have I ever hooked up in the store.
卧槽?
Really?
你们还记得乔若莎
You remember last week
上周来谈论房贷的事吗?
when Jerusha came by to talk about the mortgage?
- 在我办公室 - 哎哟 可以啊
- In my office? - Yeah, boy.
- 太恶心了 - 慢着 还有更精彩的
- Gross. - Wait, wait. There's more.
我们后来啪啪啪了
We had sex.
干得漂亮啊
Yeah, man.
小博和我
Bo and I...
七个月前... 在照片室
photo lab... seven months ago.
照片室是约炮胜地
Oh, my God, the photo lab is a great spot.
- 是呀 - 啥? 讲真?
- Yeah. - What? Really?
是啊 又暗人还少
Yeah, it's dark. It's private.
有时候你还能看到别人的裸照
Sometimes you get to see people's naked photos.
我刚在这工作的时候
When I first started here,
大家都称照片室为"炮房"
we just called the lab the "Bang room"
因为 你们懂得...
because, you know...
啪啪啪
the banging.
我在那也做过
I banged in there.
明白啦
Okay.
- 真的? - 是啊
- Really? - I did.
照片室 是吧?
So the photo lab, huh?
棒 非常棒
Cool. Cool, cool.
云九请注意...
Attention, Cloud 9...
这话筒坏了
This isn't working.
你没按下按钮
You're not pushing the button.
请注意 云...
Attention, Cloud...
- 这玩意我真是玩不溜啊 - 没错
- I really suck at this. - Yeah.
上 上 上!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
全倒
Yeah, that's a strike.
我感觉自己充满了活力
I feel alive.
云九 这是个趴地
Hey, Cloud 9, it's a party.
以后每个礼拜五都办一次
We're gonna do this every Friday from now on.
上
Go.
我可能要打破布雷特的记录了
He may just beat Brett's record time.
纵身一跃
Oh, a violent spill...
然后到了滑绳这里
and right on to the zip line.
给他点时间 他应该没事
Just give him a second. I think he's gonna be all right.
他没事
He's okay.
现在是后起之秀 马特奥...
Here we've got newcomer Mateo...
穿着云九潮到爆的睡衣
Sizzling in a fashion-forward take on Cloud 9 nightwear.
完美 马特奥 下面是格林
Work it, Mateo, and now we have Glenn,
穿着"不要让他接近你的孩子系列"
rocking the Don't Let Him Near Your Children Collection.
看格林扭着那傲人的小翘臀
Oh, shake what the good Lord gave you, Glenn,
现在是默特尔 拿着一个自行车轮胎
and here's Myrtle, carrying a bicycle tire.
她好像不懂我们在干什么
She doesn't seem to know what we're doing here,
但场面已经Hold住了
but she is owning it.
谢谢你 默特尔
Thank you, Myrtle.
艾米 你现在感觉怎么样?
So, Amy, how are you feeling?
- 棒极了 - 是吗?
- I feel great. - Oh, yeah?
一般我醉了 我说话就会很大声
Usually when I get drunk, I talk really loud,
但我现在并没有
but I'm not doing it now.
的确!
No, you're not!
各位都摇摆起来吧
All right, everybody, up on your feet.
- 你能把我打扮成她那样吗? - 像黑人妹纸?
- Can you make me look like her? - Like a black woman?
我又不是巫师
I'm not a witch.
你根本不需要那个 你已经很漂亮了
You don't need all that. You are pretty.
我妥妥的完美好吧
Oh, I'm a solid 8.25.
在高中 我在后备军官训练队是投票选出来
In high school, I was voted third-prettiest girl
第三漂亮的女孩
in my ROTC unit.
漂亮当然不是问题
Pretty's not the problem.
相信我 没错的
Just trust me.
自从我爸把我扔在加油站以后
It's just, ever since my dad left me at that gas station,
我有信任危机
it's so hard to trust.
呵呵
Okay, here we go.
未知发件人:
照片室 速来
挺精彩的
This is kind of tight.
你好啊
Hey, you.
迪娜
Dina.
- 太为她骄傲了 - 是啊
- I'm so proud of her. - Yeah.
我真没想到有这一出
Ooh, I did not see that coming,
但我应该想到的
but I should have.
"上下级之间恋爱关系
"Relationships between supervisors
现在只是不提倡了"
and subordinates is now just strongly discouraged."
并不禁止了
It's not forbidden anymore.
我俩已经不再被禁止了
This is not forbidden anymore.
是啊 呵呵
Uh, right. Yeah.
但你知道...
Uh, but, you know, s...
这是不提倡的
alas, it is discouraged.
而且和我上司谈恋爱...
Besides, the idea of dating my boss...
这性别条例太微妙了
Oof, I mean, the sexual politics are just so nuanced.
不然 相信我 我...
Otherwise, believe me, I am...
我十分愿意去...
I would love to do...
做该做的事情
everything there is to do.
我没想到会这样
I was not expecting that.
但我能理解
But I do understand.
太好了
Oh, great.
你明白就好...
I mean, you know...
你真好
Great.
好了... 那外面见
Okay, um... I'll see you out there.
你在上面干吗?
Hey, what you doing up there?
你可能会受伤啊
Looks like you might get hurt.
老娘轮不到你来教
You don't get to tell me what to do.
我不是在教你做什么
I wasn't telling you what to do.
你不是我上司 我才是你的 大学生
You are not my boss. I am your boss, college boy.
我只是觉得... 你这样有点危险...
I just thought maybe... It's a little dangerous being...
对了
By the way,
我也上大学了
I got into college too...
还是所好大学...
a good one...
我18的时候
When I was 18.
- 那很棒 - 我怀孕了
- That's great. - I just got pregnant.
然后我就结婚了 亚当有他的梦想
And then I got married, and then Adam had dreams,
那就得有人来为梦想买单
and somebody had to pay the bills,
所以我就沦落至此
so here I am,
在这没个头的地方...
spinning around on this...
浑浑噩噩...
endless...
我去
Oh, God.
不管怎么说
For what it's worth,
这比喻用得还是不错的
that was shaping up to be a really nice metaphor.
我明白了 "留个信息 然后我们永远不会回电"
Oh, I know. "Leave a message, and we'll never call you back."
这鬼话今晚行不通了 臭不要脸的
Well, that fig ain't gonna fly tonight, baby.
这公司真是丢人
This company's a sham.
你把我们关起来
You lock us in.
控制我们要听的音乐
You control the music that we listen to.
还有啊
Oh, and try this on for size.
你们这个标识牌的颜色 几乎就没变
The color difference in your signage is marginal.
你可以告诉迪克·拉森
Oh, and you can tell Dicky Larson
让他来跪舔我肥大多汁的脚指
that he can suck my big, fat, sweaty toe.
如果你确定使用此留言 请按1
If you are satisfied with your message, press 1.
删除并重录 请按2
To erase and re-record, press 2.
各位 情况一切良好
Hey, guys, everything's great.
标志牌都挂好了... 真的很好看
Signs are all up... really popping.
来 喝点
Come on.
解酒的
It's good for you.
格林说的对 这后防溅板的确不咋地
Glenn is right. This backsplash is unremarkable.
我并不后悔结婚
I don't regret getting married.
我从来没说过你后悔结...
I never said that you regretted getting...
我知道 但你心里这么想的
Yeah, but you were thinking it.
有时候我会想
Yeah, I wonder sometimes
如果当初我做了别的选择会怎样
what it would've been like if I had made other choices,
但是...
but...
我知道我后悔什么吗?
You want to know what I really regret?
最后一杯圣勃卡利口酒?
That last shot of Sambuca?
当我没说
Forget it.
你是最后一个我会告诉的人
You're the last person I should be telling this to.
慢着 为啥我是最后...
Wait. Why am I the last...
今晚太操蛋了
This is a weird night.
好
Okay.
再见啦
See ya.
出来的感觉真好
Oh, it is good to be outside.
我要回家玩电子游戏去了
I'm gonna go home and play some video games.
- 我好饿 - 要吃点早餐吗?
- I'm hungry. - You want breakfast?
我还有20分钟上班 可以给你拿杯免费咖啡
My shift starts in 20. I can get you free coffee.
我要薄烤饼
Ooh, pancakes.
我不敢相信我期中考试前一晚没睡觉
I can't believe I have to take a midterm on zero sleep
还宿醉
and totally hungover.
大学啊
College.
是啊 大学
Yep, college.
格林
Glenn.
天哪 我以为我要一个人
Oh, thank God. I thought I was gonna have
把这些东西挂起来了呢
to hang these things by myself.
- 我要求降职... - 什么?
- I'm requesting a demotion... - What?
变成普通员工... 个人因素
To associate level... personal reasons.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140
大家字幕组
啥 啥 啥?
Wha--wha--what?
哦对 这些东西的确需要两个人
And, yeah, that's gonna be a two-person job.
大家字幕组
你为啥穿的和我妈似的?
Why are you dressed like my mother?